promotingtips.com 2010-04-02

# 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

• To send periodic emails

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.promotingtips.com.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may   
contact us by emailing ->> mattbacakretires@gmail.com

We make no suggestions, implications, warranties, or guarantees that by joining this website, or that by following or adhering to any program or information featured anywhere inside this web site or elsewhere, that users will make money. We are not responsible for any losses or damages resulting from the use of any product, link, information, or opportunity contained within this web site. Users realize any business has potential risk for loss of capital. 

Furthermore, any earnings or income statements used within the website are only examples or estimates of what you could earn. There are absolutely no guarantees that you'll do as well and you must be prepared to accept the risk of doing not as well. In the event that there are any specific income or earnings figures that have been reported within the website, this must not be considered as average earnings. You must be prepared to accept the risk of doing not as well.

Earnings and income results are based on multiple factors. Every individual is different and will achieve different results. We do not know your education, experience, motivation, work ethic, as well as many other factors that may determine or affect the results of how well you may or may not do

There are absolutely no guarantees that past successes or prior results are any indication of future successes or results. The internet is a rapidly changing environment. What has worked in the past will not necessarily work in the future. Always do your own due diligence before entering into any business or making business decisions. 

By using our products and services, you agree that we are not responsible for the success or failure of your business.
